<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="styles.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<job-listing xmlns="https://spotlight-tau-three.vercel.app/" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <info>
        <title>"TERMINAL" Feature Film</title>
        <location>Location will be discussed with selected candidates.</location>
        <description>Casting and seeking crew for upcoming feature crime-thriller project.</description>
        <dates>Shoots internationally in 2025.</dates>
    </info>
    <role>
        <name>Charlotte</name>
        <type>Lead</type>
        <gender>Female</gender>
        <age>21-40</age>
        <description>An investigator entangled in a gripping murder mystery. The story follows her intense battle with a cunning serial killer, a conflict that forces her to confront and unleash her own dark side.</description>
        <ethnicity>All Ethnicities</ethnicity>
        <skills>Weapons Training: Firearms Training</skills>
        <language>English</language>
        <req-media>Headshot and Video Reel</req-media>
    </role>
    <role>
        <name>Caroline</name>
        <type>Lead</type>
        <gender>Female</gender>
        <age>18-35</age>
        <description>The main villain of the story. Looking for someone who can play strong emotions.</description>
        <ethnicity>All Ethnicities</ethnicity>
        <language>English</language>
        <req-media>Headshot/Photo</req-media>
    </role>
    <role>
        <name>Ben</name>
        <type>Lead</type>
        <gender>Male</gender>
        <age>21-40</age>
        <description>A dedicated police officer and a loyal friend who finds himself entangled in a complex case that tests his resolve. Adding to the turmoil, he becomes caught in an emotional love triangle, forcing him to navigate both personal and professional challenges.</description>
        <ethnicity>All Ethnicities</ethnicity>
        <language>English and Spanish</language>
        <req-media>Headshot/Photo</req-media>
    </role>
    <role>
        <name>Abigail</name>
        <type>Supporting</type>
        <gender>All Genders</gender>
        <age>18+</age>
        <description>A pivotal character connected to the main case as one of the victims. This is a strong supporting role that demands an actor capable of portraying deep, complex emotions and conveying the lasting impact of her experience.</description>
        <ethnicity>All Ethnicities</ethnicity>
        <language>English</language>
        <req-media>Headshot/Photo</req-media>
    </role>
        <role>
        <name>Winston</name>
        <type>Supporting</type>
        <gender>Male, Gender-Nonconforming, Non-Binary, Trans Male</gender>
        <age>50-70</age>
        <description>An introverted dreamer with a sentimental attachment to his life and surroundings. Deeply dependent on his wife, Claire, Winston struggles with change and avoids difficult conversations. He carries an emotional weight that he ultimately learns to process. Requires an actor with a wide emotional range to portray vulnerability, frustration, and eventual acceptance.</description>
        <ethnicity>Any Ethnicity</ethnicity>
        <language>English</language>
        <req-media>Headshot/Photo, Video Reel</req-media>
    </role>
</job-listing>
